by H.
Here we go...it's upgod. This time with Ayano Kawamura from Angelem,
This time, we have Ayano Kawamura from Angelem and Reina Ise from Angelem.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Kawamura, used to eat bento (boxed lunch) at our live shows due to the influence of Corona,
But from this tour, we are back to catering.
We have been served hot soup, fish, meat, white rice, and other delicious and warm dishes,
I always have a hard time deciding which one to eat,
Akane Matsumoto always tells me, "This fish tastes delicious with this flavor,
Akane Matsumoto-chan always gives me a very detailed review of the fish, saying that it tastes good with this flavor, or the meat is delicious with this seasoning,
Akane Matsumoto always gives me a very detailed review.
I always decide on the menu after listening to her reviews,
I always do my best at the concert with a lot of energy.
I sometimes think that I shouldn't eat so much because it is before the show,
But when I heard it, I thought it sounded delicious,
I also order a normal or larger amount of food,
But I make it a rule to eat at least two hours before the show,
Usually, I decide to eat two and a half hours before the show,
This makes it easier for me to move during the show,
I have decided that I will definitely eat 2 hours and a half before the show.
Also, Akane Matsumoto has influenced me in this regard,
Akane always jumps 5 times as hard as she can just before coming out from the sleeves to the stage.
She always does it.
She always does it, so I decided to learn from her and do it before going out on stage,
It is totally different when I do it and when I don't do it,
It makes it much easier to move,
I do it too, so let's do it together.
I'm doing it myself, so let's do it together.
I have my sleeves the other way around,
When I look at the sleeves on the other side of the stage before the performance, I always see a few people jumping up and down.
I always think, "Everyone is flying,
I'm sure it makes me feel lighter, so I'm going to fly before going on stage.
Let's start with this time's up-kami,
Tsubaki Factory: No mistake! No crying! Dance Lesson
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single, "It's not a mistake! I won't cry! from Tsubaki Factory's latest single, "It's not a mistake!
Let's do it while checking the choreography.
Yes. 5, 6, 7, GO!
5, 6, 7, GO!
This one should be done from the top. Not here, but from the top of the head.
And here, as I said the other day, flap your wings. Once.
Like before, this is like.......this is like.......
That's right. And then, boom, boom, boom. Slap! Like this.
That's right. Play the piano from "Do" to "Do. That's it. That's it. 5, 6, 7, 8.
Ding-dong! Charalala, 1, 2, 3, charalala, charalala. And on the sun, I like it lower.
Bend your knees over here. Not this one, this one.
And hello body. Very hello.
Talalaston! Zukka zukka, one, two, three, talalala.
Yes, everyone is low. Try to match your height with the person next to you, when you are low.
Let's match our image. I'm tall.
Let's match the big guy.
That's it. Can you do it?
But it's okay, it's okay. I like that kind of attitude.
Let's all go that far.
Come on, come on, come on, five, six, seven,
Zoom, zoom, zoom! Zucca zucca, one, two, three, talala, boom-pah!
La la la la, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Toot-toot, dah-for-lever.
Four-lever, yeah, yeah.
Yes, gentlemen, so after this...
Wait a minute!
It's like this.
You know what I mean?
It's a little bit like walking on your butt.
Hold your hips.
Hold it with your hips like this.
That's it. That's it.
Walk it like this.
Come on, chun, chara, chun, chara, ah, tattera, ah.
This leg, this way
Kakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkak
I'm not doing anything else.
Kakkakkakkak, I'm not doing anything
Kakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkakkak
Kakkakkaka, yeah, keep the leg, just the butt.
Kakkakkakka.
Yeah, come on.
I'm just pom-pom pom-pom.
Yes, yes, yes, and then just gradually climb up. Pelvis here, right side, shoulder here, just climb up three by three.
Five, six, seven, eight, here we go!Five, six, seven, eight, here we go!
Yeah, like this, nukapukkah, puchi puchi, hah, 1, 2, 3, don, hah, tarara, tarara -arara, don, tarara -arara, sarara -arara, don, kakakakkah, yeah,
Yeah, yes, one, two, three,
Ready, one!
Three, four, five,
Tattletale, tattletale,
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
I'm okay here, I'm okay here,
The singers try a little harder to express themselves.
When they move, this, this,
When you move, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this,
Movement, zucca,
Yes, yes, like this, heel and heel look right at each other,
Come on, let's go,
Talala,
Lalala, push!
Push. Push, not put. Come on, ready.
It's hard to do when it's all pinned up like this, sir. Can I bend it a little?
Ready.
Push. Knock. The ton here, there's a little bit of a thump here, and then a thump, a thump, a thump. Here, firm. Goo here, goo here, goo here.
Come on, just bring it.
Oh, my goodness, oh, my goodness, oh, my goodness, oh, my goodness, oh, my goodness, oh, my goodness, oh.
Yes, this here ha ha ha ha group.
Now Kisama wants to go outside, so I'm going to start from the back foot.
I'm on this side of you, right?
Yes, so now you're doing it right.
Because you want to go outside.
Yes, sir.
Okay, just put your right foot out.
Yes, yes, yes.
And what, I just put my inside leg in?
Yes, that's right.
Put your foot out the way you're going.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Give me a hug.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, done.
So, it's not pretty here, but it's good.
Why not? It's okay to drop out here, too.
Yes.
And here's the other part.
Yes, yes, yes. Drop out. This part is very solid.
Yes.
That's right.
No, you're dropping out too much.
But it's okay if no one else does it. It's fine.
All the time.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Yeah, yeah. So, I want to grow here.
Yeah, yeah.
So here here, so here, try to look in between.
And this, rather than going this way, get over the top.
Not diagonally, but up.
Please.
Yes, please.
Thank you for watching.
Maybe everything happens for a reason
So I'll be moving again
Let it go again, let it go again
I'll be moving again
You'll see me howling
I'll come back out again
I'll be born like you
Just like you, just like me
Let's go that way
I don't care if you're dazzling
Even at the highest levels.
Yes, it's important, the country
I'm going to fall in love with you.
Come on, look up.
There's no mistaking it.
I'm in love with you.I fell in love with you.
I'm sure of it
Though it still hurts now
I'll always love you
Till we grow into two
That I can cherish
I don't fall in love less
It's not just that I've lost
I can't cry
Doing what you did
The world has changed
No regrets, no love
Embrace the future
This song, "No Mistake, No Crying," is about changing from a girl to an adult while falling in love,
Tsubaki Factory has a lot of songs about love, but this song is the most mature among them,
The dance has a lot of mature choreography, and there are many places where we all have to play together,
I was very conscious of the fact that all 10 of us were expressing one music while each of us was expressing our individuality in our dance lessons.
Kishimoto's point of interest is that there are a lot of English lyrics in the song.
Especially in the intro, outro, and the middle of the chorus,
Among the various members singing, Marin Fukuda, who is good at English, was in charge of many of them,
She sings the English part like a rap song by herself,
Of course, her English pronunciation and such are cool,
But it is also cool to see how powerful and bold Marin is when she dances while speaking English.
I think this fits the theme of the song, from a girl to an adult,
I felt Marin's growth from the previous single to this single,
I really felt Marin's growth from the previous single to this single, so I hope you will pay attention to it.
When I saw her dancing for the first time, I thought it was really cool that she was dancing so well together,
But when I saw the dance lesson, I realized that the dancers were all dancing together,
When they open their hands, they press the piano's "Do" as if they were pressing the "Do" from the piano's "Do",
That's what Angeleum often tells us in the dance lesson,
I thought that when the hands were so open, it made it look like everyone's hands were in perfect alignment.
I was watching this dance lesson, and the choreographer, Yuka-sensei, is also in charge of Angels,
I don't know if it's the same when she sings the solo part,
I don't know if it's the same when I sing a solo part, but there are many times when I have to think up the choreography on my own,
This time, I think there may be some choreographed scenes in the solo parts, but I think there were some scenes where I had to come up with my own choreography,
I think there were some scenes where we had to come up with the choreography by ourselves,
Comparing those scenes with ours, I would often overthink things and end up looking a bit unnatural,
But I felt that everyone in Tsubaki's group moved their hands so naturally,
I thought it was very cool and smooth.
That's all I have to say about Tsubaki Factory's no-cry dance lesson.
No one can pollute the night sky, the night sky is watching over you.
Beyonce New Single Yomeshinai Yozora no Yume wo Kantekiranai Now on sale
Thank you for all your hard work.
Next, here it is: Beyonce Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, Instrumental Recording
Here is a video of Beyonce's latest single, "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler," recorded on bass.
The aim of this recording is to have the A and B parts bouncing around, and the chorus is more of a legato.
So, it might be better to connect the notes in the chorus.
I understand.
This one is brighter or more grainy.
Let's go with this one then.
Let's go for more and more in life.
I've always wanted to be useful in the future.
I don't really have a style.
I don't have much style, but I'll give it a try.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I'm going. I'm going to play small fish.
Out, out, out, geometry, voila.
200 meters each. Divide the distance by the target.
25 minutes.
Every month, Mr. Destiny's Traveler.
If you anticipate coincidences and reserve miracles here...
add up, add up, add up, just the two of us meeting
Guided by the hand by my side
Every month, Mr. Destiny's Traveler
Seek more of life
Let's seek more travel
I'm on duty, I'm on duty, I'm on duty, I'm on duty, I'm on duty
I'll give it to you, I'll give it to you, I'll give it to you, I'll give it to you
I just want you to laugh
Life, it's all about more, more, more
I'll dance for you
I've been having so much fun
Cause I want you to laugh
Life, I want more and more and more
Fortune-telling palapa Fortune-telling palapa
Fortune-telling, fortune-telling, fortune-telling
addition, addition, subtraction, subtraction
Chips, chips, splits, splits
I think I want to make the A melody a little more bouncy.
Do-do-do-do start do-do-do-do-do do-do-do-doDo-do-do-do-do start do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do
DODODODOLI DODODOLI DODODOLI DODOLI DODOLI DODOLI DODOLI DODOLI DODOLI DODOLI DODOLI
Dododoped! every time you do it.
If you do it once, it might be a little noisy.
Then do it three times, and only play the fourth time.
Maybe you should play it twice.
Let's start with the A melody.
Yes, I'm going to introduce you to these 10 people at the same time.
Let's find out how many will be when they meet!
It doesn't make sense.
I always said I'd be useful in the future.
I don't have much in the way of real style.
It's good, isn't it? Let's go next time.
Okay, let's go next.
I guess we'll go next then.
makeup
goo
me
I wanted you to laugh at my life, I want more and more and more and more
To the man in question
The groove was good in the second half, so maybe you should just get the first half.
25 minutes later
Everyone, travellers of destiny...
Let's make a miracle happen.
Please sit down. How can I meet you if I don't believe in you?
I'll put my hand on you and guide you.
Everyone
Yes, it's perfect.
Are you okay?
And if you said we'd take pictures afterwards, I'd like to take about four of these.
Of course. I'll see what I can do.
That's good, isn't it?
Can I do it one more time while singing that song?
Yes, you may.
Thank you for watching.
OK, let's go next!
Okay, D.
Yes, D. Can I do it one more time?
Yes, of course.
See you soon!
Sorry ahhh Перв was good have you
lur
I think it's good. It's finished.
My name is Shigeru Murata, bass player.
I enjoyed it. Thank you very much.
I was looking forward to it because it was a song by Beyonce, whom I originally liked.
Moreover, it was a song by Sho Hoshibe, and I was very moved to be able to play it in the way that it has Mr. Hoshibe's verses, but with the bass in fine detail.
The problem was that I could hear the members singing while I was listening.
I listen to it too much. I try not to listen to that while I play the bass guitar.
I tried to put only my soul into the music, as if I was making music.
In terms of the technical part, I tried to include the 16 fine details and the feathers in a comfortable way.
I believe that the best music is made when you are in the groove, so I put emphasis on that aspect of the music.
The part I want you to pay attention to is right before the "tete tete tete tete tete" at the end of the first chorus.
It appears three times in this song, and I put everything I had into those three times.
If you just pay attention to that part, the rest of the song itself is great. I hope you enjoy it.
I look forward to this instrumental recording every time, and this time it's the bass guitar,
I often think that the bass is very effective in cute or bright songs,
When I first heard this song, I had the impression that the bass sounded great,
When I watched the video again, I got the impression that the bass was playing all the time without a break, which I thought was amazing,
I was really impressed by the way they were playing with such a groove, and I was also impressed by the way they were playing,
I also thought it would be different if I listened to the video after watching it, so I wanted to listen to it again.
I would like to listen to it again,
The song "Tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete,
I could hear the bass guitar playing "tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete tete,
I listened to it so much and practiced so much that I could play it with my eyes closed,
I could feel how much fun it was to play, and I could feel that fun in the sound,
I think that the joy of playing the song is conveyed in the sound, and it makes the song shine even more brightly.
That's all for Beyonce, Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, bass recording.
Enjoying it? Please check out the rest.
With Ayano Kawamura of Angulum,
Up-cam by Ayano Kawamura of Angeleum and Reina Ise of Angeleum,
Here's the next one.
Ocha-no-Man Nanami Kubota's makeup lecture.
This is Nanami Kubota's makeup lecture.
This time, she is practicing eye makeup using brown colors.
Let's take a look.
This is Nanami Kubota from Ocha-no-Ma.
Today I'd like to do a makeup using brown eye shadow, which I do during my live performances.
Yay! It's a kirurun makeup.
Yes, so I am nervous, but I will do my best!Yes, so I am nervous, but I will do my best!
I would like to start right away.
This time, we are going to focus on eye makeup, so I have already finished foundation, eyebrows, and rippers.
So, let's get started.
First, I will mix the light colors from this palette, white and beige, and apply them to the entire eyehall.
The key point here is to apply the powder to the eyes after blending it in with your arm.
You can apply it to pretty much the entire body.
I always apply it to the upper eyehall only.
Next, I would like to mix the darker shade with the darker shade and apply it to the double width of the eye.
I would apply it darker on the outer corner of the eye, but at this point, it is still fine to apply it all together.
Mix the darkest and lightest colors and apply so that the darker color is applied to the outer corner of the eye.
The darkest color is the darkest at this point, so make sure to blend it in with your arm before applying.
At this time, I always apply eyeliner to the lower part of the eye, rather than the wider horizontal part.
So, if you draw eyeliner horizontally, apply it to the side eyes.
I think it's better to apply it broadly.
I got the top eyeshadow like this.
Then next, I'd like to go to the bottom.
For the bottom, I want to apply this light pink eyeshadow first.
I would like to apply this light pink eyeshadow to the entire tear trough.
By applying pink eyeshadow
The pink eyeshadow will make the tear troughs look fuller.
I recommend it.
Then, mix the black part of this eyeshadow
I want to draw a line for the tear troughs.
I think it is important to note that some people use pens or tear trough pens to draw tear troughs,
In my case, the tear troughs are quite wide vertically, so using a pen would make them float, so the key is to draw them with a thin brush.
I drew the tear trough line on the place where I smiled.
At this point, I'm probably wondering if it's okay to draw them this wide.
I will do my best to shorten them later, so it is okay to draw them wider.
Draw the eyeliner.
This is the eyeliner that all the members of Ochanoma use.
The eyes are like this, and it is important to lower the eye line so that it connects to this circle.
When it reaches about the same height as here, I stop.
I think the longer the eyeliner is, the cuter it looks, so I draw a lot of eyeliner.
Next time, I will draw eyeliner.
Using this thin brush I used earlier, I'm going to draw the eyeliner.
I'm going to use this thin brush to draw in the eyeliner.
I'm going to blur it out.
At this point, take the black shadow you just used and blend it in like this.
and blend it like this to get a good look.
I'm going to use this pink liner.
Use this pink liner called "Nemo" and trace under the eyes.
Add a touch of blood color.
I'm going to use this pink Ina concealer to make the tear ducts look fuller.
Use a brush to apply it to the tear troughs.
The point here is to put it on the corner of the eye.
I don't put it on the corner of the eye, I put it on the highest part of the eye and gradually spread it out.
So be careful not to apply it to the crease of the eye.
Once you've applied it, just use the blood-colored liner again.
It will be fine.
For the crease of the eye
Straight from the eyeliner to the middle of the eye like this.
I think it will look prettier if you don't use concealer to fill in the crease of the eye.
Even if you fill it in, you can fix it with eyeshadow later.
It's okay if you fill it in, you can fix it later with eyeshadow.
Can you see how I made her mouth a little fuller?
Take a light pink eyeshadow and put it under your eyes.
Put it on the lower part of your eyes.
You can use brown or pink, whichever you like.
I used a brown eye shadow and put it on the lower part of my eyes.
As I said before, I want to draw a straight line from the eye line to the top of the middle of the eye line.
It's okay if you just feel like it.
This is the kind of eyeshadow that many idols use to make their tear ducts look fuller.
You can use any kind of eye shadow, but I used a pinkish one with fine lamé.
Take this and apply it to the tear troughs on the inner corner of the eye and the outer corner of the eye.
Can you see it? It makes them look fuller.
It gives a three-dimensional effect.
This is the most important point.
I use this Sezanne highlighter. I often ask people what kind of highlighter they use, and I think there are a lot of people who use this. I think there are a lot of people who use this when I ask them what they use for highlighter.
If you put the glitter at the top of the tear ducts, it gives a great three-dimensional effect. I've been asked what I'm actually using and what I'm applying.
I take a very thin brush and apply it on the highest point.
I take a very thin brush and apply it to the highest part of the eye, just a little bit open from the edge of the eye.
I'm going to apply lame.
Since it's a live performance, I'm going to apply this bejeweled lame.
I'm going to blend it in by tapping it on my finger, and then I'm going to apply it in the middle, on the double line.
We are going to do the lashes, the important, important lashes.
The nailer is applied firmly around the eyes and then lifted upwards with a gentle pressure.
Then, I don't want to make my lashes too thick.
I use this mascara.
I don't need to apply any primer or mascara primer.
I like it a lot because it keeps all day long!I love it so much because it stays on all day long!
First, I'll apply it using the thinner side of this bottom one.
Next, I use the thicker one on the opposite side and tease it sideways to make a bunch.
When you get a nice bunch, use the tweezers. I like to use the curved tweezers because they are the easiest to use on the eyes.
This should be done before the mascara dries, so it's a pretty quick game there.
Then, since my tear troughs are quite wide, I'm going to do the lower lashes as well to make them look natural.
I'm going to use this for the lower lashes as well.
I'll use the one with the deeper and longer zigzags I mentioned earlier.
I'm going to do my best to extend the lashes from the outer half of the eye.
If you have trouble extending your lower lashes, you can extend them a lot by putting them up here and here.
So, the eye makeup is now complete.
Can I ask one more thing?
I've been getting a lot of people asking me, "Which blush do you use? I'd like to introduce my blush.
I'd like to introduce blush.
What! It's a super pink blush!
I don't know if it's a good match since I don't use brown blush.
But I get asked about it a lot, so I'm going to use it today.
I think you can use any kind of brush.
Use a brush that is not too thick.
I have a round face.
I put it on the side of my face.
I put it on the side of my face, but the darkest part is in the center of the face.
I put it on the side of my face, but the darkest part is in the center of my face.
Kubo and Anatami.
So, my eye makeup and make-up are done!
Yay! How do you like it? Is it nice and soft?
Curururun!
Yes, I think my point is...
I think eye makeup should be, how should I say it?
Don't apply each shadow too thickly.
Don't apply too much shadow.
Use a lot of shadows.
I use a lot of shadows and put on a little bit of each one that suits each place.
I think that if you give a three-dimensional effect to the face, it will look a little more natural.
As I mentioned earlier, I put highlights on the top of the face, and that's what I like to do.
Let's have a nice face! That's all for now, this is Nanami Kubota from Ochanoma!
Bye bye!
Nanami Kubota, I've always thought your eyes were really cute and round, so I'm glad I was able to show you how they're made.
The reason for the curl is that she made the tear troughs really firm, and that's what makes them so special.
I learned a lot about how to put concealer on after applying this, and how to use a thin brush for the shadow line of the tear ducts, etc. I've been wondering about tear ducts, so I've been trying to imitate her makeup.
I'd like to try to imitate them.
Yes, Nanami Kubota does a lot of her eye makeup with a brush, and I was really impressed by how carefully she does her makeup.
I've never used a brush because I find it too much of a hassle, so I thought I'd like to try it.
I also wanted to use the same cosmetics that you use, so I thought I would like to try using them as a reference for my own makeup.
That was the makeup lecture by Nanami Kubota, the tea no-man.
ANGELUM
Angelem's new album "Pick Club! NOW ON SALE!
Welcome back!
It's time to say goodbye to upcami, the show presented by Ayano Kamimura and Reina Ise.
We have seen a lot of different images this time,
I, Ise, was very impressed with the first dance lesson by Tsubaki Factory,
I think it is partly because we had the same choreographer for this dance,
The choreography of the introduction of this song was very impressive,
The choreography of the introduction of this song was very impressive, and I could tell that they must have practiced a lot,
The intro of this song was very impressive, and I could tell that they must have practiced a lot,
We also have a lot of dances with distinctive intros and dances in which everyone joins together,
I hope we can learn from their example and do the same with our choreography.
I, Kawamura, attended Nanami's make-up class at the tea ceremony,
I watched this video over and over again and bought the same makeup tools,
I will watch this video over and over again, buy the same makeup tools, and do my best to become a "kyururun.
In UpCami, we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we will introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time, up-cami is with Ayano Kawamura of Angulum,
and Reina Ise from Angeleum.
Good bye!
Next time on Up-Kami,
Beyonce, let's seek! and Fate's Traveler's recording session.
And,
recording for Angelem's latest album, Big Love.
Enjoy!
Strong Place and Burn